May 21, Anjo City, Aichi Prefecture
Cute as an ogre, a kettle vendor suddenly appeared like a summer typhoon!
I'm going to be a baker!
Which is which?
It was a dream, but I'm a baker.
Love tuning
Cute!
Thank you.
You don't have bread, do you? Fresh.
Delicious.
This is how it usually works.
This story is a miracle born of a can.
There really are a lot of people here.
Houses are lined up in rows.
I'm going to put a mosaic.
Yes, I'll put a mosaic. I'm sorry.
It's amazing, really.
Because all of these strokes are occupied.
All of them.
I'll put a mosaic.
It's like this.
You can't see it.
This... bread paper...
I've never seen this much before.
The parking lot was full.
It was amazing.
Just bread?
Bread!
This line was not formed for them.
Actually, the other day
We went to Bread Tiger for a Youtube shoot.
Do you remember what we did? At the Bread Tiger.
We had breakfast and chatted.
We chatted over breakfast. We chatted and chatted and chatted.
I'm sorry, I was going to use bread to describe who I like.
Salty bread. Salty is good.
I was writing something at the time.
In the "Good and Nice" section, there's this... Opinion Bottle.
Opinion forms, what kind of bread you like to eat...
I've been trying my best to develop and offer products I haven't really been to, but...
That's great, tell me about it. I'm embarrassed. Gorrity Gate.
I've done that. I've done marketing and stuff.
I do marketing and stuff like that. You like that?
Like that.
I couldn't believe my eyes when Sakamoto started drawing pictures instead of opinions.
Bread? I've never seen bread like this.
I think I'll go with moon... moon buns.
The theme is the moon.
Basically, it's curry bread. It's dotted with dots.
Curry buns? Yes, the main one is curry bread.
The middle one.
In the middle.
Let's see...
Two different flavors
Yes, sir.
I think it's a little bit hard to make.
Yes, but if you can enjoy two different flavors in one loaf.
That's right. And it's basically just curry.
And here, next to it, there's a cheese that grows on you.
Stretchy cheese!
Cheese.
And cheese and something else.
Avocado.
Oh, that's good.
But not if it's hot.
Curry? Natto?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, of course.
I'll have natto then.
Then natto.
I'll have cheese.
I'll have cheese, and I'll have tsubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubutubu.
I don't know how long I've been able to eat curry
I learned the joy of toppings
Natto's good, too.
It's delicious.
I've never had natto.
Have you had natto?
One bean
Natto
I fell.
Fell?
I forgot the fall.
Moon Bread
Moon Curry Bread?
Moon Curry Bread.
I want ice cream.
Coronet was like this, right?
Yes.
So, on the regular menu here.
They had coronets, chocolate coronets.
Yeah, there was. That looked delicious.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here's a regular chocolate coronet.
On top of this.
Soft serve ice cream
On top of it.
And then...
I wanted to make a perfect match.I wanted to make it look sharp, so I put colored chocolate on top.
Color chocolate on top.
Chocolate spray
or chocolate sauce on top
Popping is my favorite!
Little one.
This is my new product, Amber!
De-da-da-da-da!
Korosofu
Sakamoto may have just wanted to make the hard-to-eat curry bread and natto easier to eat.
Of course, Akimoto just wanted to eat ice cream.
However...
Tora-san, a fan, contacted us and told us that they decided to commercialize the product.
Ha-ha-ha!
So, let's see...
Which one?
Let's see...
What? What?
We're going to commercialize it.
Wow, that's great!
Isn't it great?
And it's not like we were forced to do it or anything,
Mr. Akimoto and Mr. Sakamoto of the Kasugai store were probably in charge of the product,
On the same day, they collect the opinion boxes, right?
Yes, yes.
And they usually take them,
And I got a call saying, "Well, I see.
That's great.
And they said yes.
Oh, you mean the photo? I said, "Yes, it's from the photo.
Ha-ha-ha!
That's great.
Well, we talked about it, and, actually, it will be a new product starting in June,
Well, the fan is going to be a new product starting in June.
Ha-ha-ha!
And...,
I'm laughing! LOL!
Is it real?
It's real! I thought, "It's real!
Yes, it's real.
Amazing!
So, I wanted to present a video of the two of you,
I wanted to make a presentation of what I told you both in the video,
I'm doing it now.
Wow, wow, wow!
I wasn't sure if it would really pass or not.
I thought it wouldn't.
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it would pass at all.
I was serious, but I was thinking about it.
I thought about it, I thought about it.
I didn't think it would pass at SandCaracter's meeting.
You were mentioned in the meeting?
Ha-ha-ha!
Wait, wait, wait!
Maybe it's okay.
So, as of now,
As of today,
As of today, May 10,
except for Fan-no-Tora Okazaki Service Area Store.
What? Wait, wait!
Not just a little crumb in it?
Yes.
Five stores?
Five stores,
Isn't that great?
Wait, that's really crazy.
I'm amazing.
I'm laughing.
It's amazing.
It's a commercialized panda.
It will be here.
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh, my.
There it is!
It's exactly as Uta wrote!
It's exactly as Uta wrote it.
Wait, wait! Did you make it already?
I thought the picture would come out?
You already made it?
That's great!
I gave you another one.
Huh!
It's in there like this.
And, uh, yes.
You have natto written on it.
Yes, I have natto written on it.
Natto Curry Bread
It's a curry bun called Nihon Curry Bread
I'm making a Bugaku Kyoku.
Bugaku-kyoku?
This is not good!
Wait a minute, this is amazing!
This is amazing!
I'm so impressed. I'm so surprised.
This is amazing.
It's so real. It's so real.Real, this is real.
It's really real.
It's not a fake.
It's really, really, really great.
So, I'm going to go see the president.
I'd like to meet you in person.
Let's talk about all kinds of things.
Yes, please meet with him.
Okay, I'll be there.
I'll be there.
And the day I came to sample Moon Curry Bread
The day of this huge line
At the same time, the bread tigers were making a Guinness World Records attempt.
The challenge was to sell 2475 loaves in the first two hours.
The number of loaves sold in the first two hours of the event was 2,475.
They were challenging the Guinness Book of World Records for the most curry buns sold in a 24-hour period.
It's another complicated day for a tasting.
Let's go to the back of the store.
The back side is also stylish!
There's a garden, too.
Excuse me.
Moon Curry Bread in the back of the big line.
This way please.
The one who's speaking now is the bread's developer.
Is this Moon Curry Bread?
Yes.
You can see what's inside.
Thank you for watching.
Is it what I envisioned?
Well, I wouldn't want to see that.
It's amazing. It's in this bag of pantographs.
Of course it is.
Wow! Wow!
The shape is amazing!
It's just like it!
Wait a minute.
What do you think? Can I get that out?
What do you think?
The shape...
Oh, my God! It's beautiful!
I love it!
Thank you very much.
That's great.
It's okay.
Smells great.
I wanted long, thin curry buns.
Basically, the boss asks me if I can make a product like this, and all I get is weird stuff.
Is that so? What do you think about that, boss?
For example, let's say you make a delicious cheese, natto, and curry bun.
Then it's just an ordinary product that looks good, but...
But if you want people to pick it up, the appearance is also important, isn't it?
And also the name.
That's why the recipient feels it's strange.
May I try some?
Eat.
I'll have some curry buns.
Here comes Nat!
Delicious!
Delicious and easy to eat!
Bon appétit!
Here comes Nat!
I'm discounting it by a thousand yen.
Actually, this was just a product idea.
I had two parts of the curry, the natto curry part and the cheese curry part.
This one is also divided into two parts.
So
This side is natto.
This side, is it natto?
Natto?
Let's just pinch a little bit.
What?
Mmm. Delicious.
Delicious.
Easy to eat.
Curry buns are very tasty, but...
But the timing of eating it...
I want curry! Curry buns! I have a little bit of make-up around my mouth
I put a little bit of make-up around my mouth
I can't help but get some on my mouth.
But it's beautiful.
I can eat it beautifully.
And I've always hated curry.
I used to hate curry when I was little.
I've been able to eat it for a couple of years now.
I suddenly became able to eat it.
And from there, the amount of time I couldn't eat it before
I've been able to eat curry at an accelerated pace.
I go out for curry every week to make up for it.
I went to eat curry every week as if I was trying to make up for it.
Then I found out there were toppings.
Pork shabu-shabu, cheese, etc.
I realized that natto goes well with a lot of toppings like pork shabu-shabu and cheese.
I often make natto curry at home.
I thought it was delicious.
Cheese!
Wow! So fast!
Delicious!Delicious.
I'd like you to tell me if you have any improvements or requests.
I'd like to see something a little more like this.
If you have any
I don't see anything
I don't see anything to improve.
I really don't see anything.
Smaller grains of natto (fermented soybeans)
The grains are big, aren't they?
Yes, it is.
I dared to make them bigger this time.
If it says "natto" on the label, I'll look for it.
I'd be happier if it had larger grains.
When I looked for it earlier, I was happy to find some grains.
So I felt like I could really feel the natto.
That's right.
It's better to have it there than not to find it at all.
It's easier to understand.
That's good.
We're going to start selling them on June 1st.
Now that you're here, we'd like to make it a pre-sale.
Yes, when we can.
Pre-sale?
I'm helping out tomorrow with the Guinness Curry Bread.
I'm very grateful. Thank you very much.
I'd like to pre-launch the Moon Curry Bread as well.
We'd like you to hear what kind of response we get when we actually hand them out.
We'd like to receive your feedback and decide whether we should rearrange it a little bit or not.
We'd like to decide whether we'll rearrange it a bit or keep it as is.
It's nice to be given the bread in person.
The next day, four bakers were summoned.
I've always dreamed of being a baker. It's my bakery debut!
Bakery debut, first time for all of us today!
And it's Yuzuki's and Honne's first time.
That's right, Yuzuki, we're practicing for when you become an old man.
You've become an old man.
I want to be a baker.
I'll leave it here for a minute.
It's a nice reflection of the sky.
It's pretty narrow.
It's so small.
We'll make it. You want to see us make it?
This is already made by professionals.
Akimoto and Daikoku will be selling a bread called "Chilled French Toast.
Remember, Akimoto invented bread too!
It's called Korosof.
I wonder if they took pity on Akimoto
The Pantora people made an iced bread that bears no resemblance to Korosof.
In contrast to Korosov Akimoto, Sakamoto looked very proud.
Korosov Akimoto's start was severely cut short, but this is the reality of the situation.
Thank you very much.
Please eat well. Please let me know what you think.
But Akimoto is a man with a heart of steel.
I'll put ice cream on it.
I got the ice cream!
Is it okay to put it at an angle? Is it going to fall off?
Bailey, are you going to fall?
Well, if he falls off, if he falls off...
If I fell, I fell.
That's not what happened.
Hi, Bailey.
Hey, Pom.
Moon bread?
I bought some moon bread.
Moon bread looks delicious.
Take a selfie with moon bread.
Here you go.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Moon.
You know who I am.
Moon, right?
But I can eat natto.
But it's delicious.
It's delicious.
I'll have it with my favorite sea french.
Bon appétit.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
I'm off.
Have a good day.
Be careful.
Thank you.
I want you two to work your magic and make it taste good.
Okay.
I'm almost done.
I'll do it.
Doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle.
Is that it?
Doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doodle doo
Love new!
Do it with me.
Let's do it together.
Love Thursday
Cute!
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Here you go.Here you go.
Thank you.
It's a little bit of a balancing act.
Here you go.
Hey, there.
Hi, there.
All right.
Let's put ice cream on it.
Here you go.
You can put a lot of ice cream on it.
No, you can't.
Yes!
Wow, you're good.
I'm getting good at this.
I see.
Good!
You're doing great.
You're doing great!
It looks delicious.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Please take this one, too.
I have a customer.
Of course.
I also have a birthday party.
That's right.
You said you had something for me.
Yes, I did.
I'd love to see you.
You and your guests.
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome to this one, too.
Thank you.
Let's go get two.
Two?
Thank you for standing in line in the heat.
Thank you.
I recommend these clothes.
A basket?
One.
One?
They look so much alike.
I'm having too much fun today.
I went to bed early.
Woke up early one more time and waited forever.
What? Why?
Thank you.
It's open. It's open.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you looking through here?
Come on in.
I see it.
Can I ask you to get that for me?
Just a little bit.
He's so cute.
I'll put the ice cream on.
Here you go.
Ice cream.
They make it for you.
The problem is this.
Berries.
Fruit?
Oh, no, they're rolling.
Ice cream.
You like ice cream?
I love ice cream.
Panner.
It's sweet powder.
It's sweet, sweet powder.
It's sweet.
Okay, then.
Let's see if I can get it.
Can you get it?
Are you okay?
Mommy, please.
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Okay.
Are you okay? I'm fine. Thank you.
Not yet.
Curry buns again.
Curry bun.
Next, French Curry Bread.
Next.
Can you eat that much?
If you don't show up...
I don't know what I'll do.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
I'm afraid to look at him.
During the show
Yoo-hoo!
Thank you.Thank you.
You should eat.
Thank you.
Three pieces.
Thank you. Thank you.
Look how big you've grown.
Oh, my gosh.
Come again.
Thank you. Thank you.
You should eat.
Thank you so much.
That was really good.
Thank you. Feeling good?
Feeling good?
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
You know what?
I really like your outfit.
Oh, really?
It's cute.
Thank you.
Please eat.
Is this good?
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
Is it?
Sakura is always hungry, like always.
Thank you. Was it good?
It was good.
Oh, really?
I'm glad.
It's good, isn't it? It's delicious.
You've never seen it in bread before.
It's delicious.
You haven't seen it in bread.
Fresh
The view is delicious.
Now it's moving like this.
Nice, nice.
Tahmimin's moving like this.
Sales are going great too
Moon Curry Bread and Kolosov, or cold French toast
and Korosof, or rather, chilled French toast
sold out!
Delicious!
That's great!
It's nice to see it in person.
It's not often you get to see people eating bread in a tight group.
It was really interesting.
It was great to see so many people here.
Thank you very much.
Please let us know what you think of the bread by including the name of the product or the name of the bread and the hashtag, and we'd love to hear your feedback!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!
Sorry for the wait, Sakura!
You can finally eat it!
Bye bye!
Dad.
Thank you.
Wow!
Yes. Tuk Choa Khamo.
Wow! Yum!
Yum!
I've been wanting some for a while now.
Bon appétit!
Yuzuki and Hou-chan were cooking
Yes!
On the kitchen car side
French toast!
cool!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Really delicious!
It's great!
I hope people will like it when they eat it.
Hey, the bread is delicious to begin with.
I didn't dye the bread.
It's good?
Yeah, it is.
You forgot to talk.
She eats too much.
She works hard at eating.
Delicious.
I can't get enough of it
Delicious
It's good to have a snack
Because Haru-chan loves snacks
They are so delicious!
I'm glad. Thank you very much.
Delicious.
This is ?
This is the Moon Curry Bread that was on sale today!
Moon Curry Bread
This time, it was on sale in advance.
JuneJun.
Jun.
June
Featured product
We buy and eat the highlight of the month.
It's the highlight of the month.
It smells really good.
So let's all eat it.
I ate it.
It's warm.
It's so good.
Hot.
Natto.
I think it's cheese.
Delicious.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Natto! Natto!
It's so good!
It's so good, but natto!
Oh, my God.
There's some pretty good pasta!
It's so good!
Very tasty natto!
Delicious!
Well, Momoro, that's the third one today.
Isn't that cheating?
Natto is sweet.
Yes, it is.
If it's natto and cheese at Pareap, I'm a little more excited about the cheese.
Natto for the win!
The natto grains are all piled up on the bottom.
The last bite of the natto, and then the natto grains start to come up...
Oh, I see.
That's what I wanted!
Oh, my God!
I can't take it anymore.
I'm doing it all over again.
I'm going crazy.
This is delicious.
I'm not going out looking for it.
Yusaki put curry buns on it.
She went to look for curry bread.
My friend NT Stasz
But it was already gone.
patches
This cute version is called "사실 bastard
Oh!!!
I'm so happy!
Finish your new search with me!
Please subscribe to our virtual channel!
Also, each LudgBeat bastante of 별로 guideline bar chan
Close by
Shibuya Japan TV
And the Guinness for the most number of curry buns sold
We, Team Ceci, are the first girl group in Aichi Prefecture, so
We were asked to help Panotara's Curry Bread Guinness World Record attempt.
We participated in the event this time.
By the time we were ready to help, the curry bread had already been sold out!
We were really impressed by the fact that this bakery is loved by everyone in the town.
The curry buns were already sold out!
Congratulations to Mr. Kang's Tiger for achieving the Guinness World Records!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Good job. Good job.
Bye bye bye
It was a nice space
Hey, it was fun, wasn't it?
Hey, we all get along so well!
Hey, I knew it!
The atmosphere is so nice
It was full of warm smiles.
It was very moving.
I don't think I've ever witnessed such a moment in my life.
It's true, it's a real honor to be here.
I was honored to be able to witness each and every one of them.
I got a lot of energy from it.
Until the very end.
It was hot, but everyone was warm.
Hey, I'm really chubby!
Hey, you guys are so fun!
You guys look so happy!
We will continue to be your
We are fans of fan tigers!
Fan of fan tigers
We are fans
We're all in this together
I hope we can help out again.
I'm sure we will.
I'll buy and eat on my own.
I hope we can be friends again.
Yes, I'll be happy if we can continue to be friends.
Congratulations
Congratulations!
And by the way, you guys...
It was delicious!Hey, it was delicious.
It was so good!
I can't wait to try it again.
You should try it, too!
I'll definitely eat it.
I'll definitely eat it!
It was born out of a chance encounter
It was a connection with a fan, Tora-san.
It was an irreplaceable experience for them.
I think it was an invaluable experience.
Please eat it!
Please eat!
Please, please, please.
They're so energetic.
They've been playing all morning.
Peace with everyone.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
If you like what you see, please click the "Good" button.
Subscribe to our channel
Please leave a comment.
That's all for now.
This is SHARES.
bye-bye!
Tara
Tara.
ba-boom
bye-bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Please subscribe to our channel.
[Please subscribe to our channel.